안녕하세요, 척이에요
몇 가지 아셔야 할 게 있어요
싫음 말고요
헤어지려는건 아니지?
그거 다시 돌려주세요
새라랑 난 지금 관계 이상으로
발전하지 않을거야
머리 속에 풀크럼에 대한
정보가 들어간거 같아요
이 놈은 시체 안치실로
누구 무덤이죠?
Who's the stiff?
CIA 처리장에 묻혀있던 브래드 화이트의
The corpse was dug up from a CIA dump site.
무덤이 파헤쳐져 있었네
The grave belonged to Brad White.
척에게 인터섹트 테스트를 했던
풀크럼 요원 중 한 사람이네요
That's one of the FULCRUM agents who ran the Intersect test on Chuck.
왜 풀크럼에서 그런 짓을 한거죠?
Why would they rob his grave?
자네들 임무가 그걸 알아오는 거네
That's what we need you to find out.
훔쳐간 게 형세에 변화가 생길만한
정보라는 정보를 입수했어
We picked up chatter that whatever they took
is potentially game-changing intelligence.
You want us to grab Chuck,keep him underground?
척을 데리고 숨어 지내란 말씀이십니까?
I don't think that's necessary yet,
지금 당장은 그럴 필요까진 없지만
but keep a close eye on the asset until we have further information.
정보를 더 입수하기 전 까지는
곁에서 잘 보살피도록 하게
척에게서 눈을 떼지 말도록 해
Don't let him out of your sight.
척, 새라 전환데
안 받을거야?
Chuck,it's Sarah.Don't you want to answer it?
아 그게, 어차피..
Oh,you know,I'm going to...
나중에 만날텐데 뭐
see her later anyway, so...
그래
Yeah.
가끔은 좀 튕겨주기도 해야지
Sometimes you got
to play hard to get.
무심하면서 멀리 하는게
엄청난 최음제가 될 수 있다고
Cold and detached is a very
powerful aphrodisiac, babe.
금욕도 마찬가지지
So is abstinence.
한번 해볼래?
You want to try it?
난 이만 손 뗄게
Not getting involved.
척, 네가 저번에 새라 얘기 했었잖아
Chuck,
the other night,
you said some pretty
heavy things about Sarah,
인연이 아닌 것 같다고 한거
about her not being the one.
응, 그냥 문제가 좀 있는 것 뿐이야
Well, you know, I mean,
we've got our issues.
걱정할 것 없어, 누나
다 괜찮아질거야
But don't... don't
worry, sis; it will all
work itself out.
아냐, 척
그렇지 않을거야
No, Chuck,
it won't.
너 매일 그렇게 말하는데
That's what you
always say, you know.
앞으로 나아가려면
네 인생을 스스로 관리할 줄 알아야지
You have to take control
of your life if you want TO MOVE FORWARD.
바이모어에서도 잠깐 일한다고 해놓고
You said you'd work
at the Buy More temporarily.
벌써 5년이나 됐잖아
It's been...
it's been five years.
그게, 새라랑 헤어지는게
그렇게 쉽지가 않아
It's-it's just...
it's not so easy breaking up
with Sarah Walker, you know.
일이 좀 복잡해
It's, uh...
it's a little complicated.
알아
I know.
나도 알아
나도 새라 좋아해
I know, and I love Sarah.
하지만 새라가 네 인연이 아니라면
I just think
that if she's not the one,
새라한테 얘기해야해
you got to tell her.
이건 새라한테 상처 주는 건 둘째치고
You're not just
hurting her.
네 자신에게도 상처를 주는 거야
You're hurting
yourself.
밤에 잠도 못 자게 만드는 사람하고
Dude, do you have any idea what it's like
to be in a relationship
같이 지내는게 어떤지 알아?
that's so upsetting
that it just keeps you up at night?
대충 알 것 같다
Vaguely familiar.
모르는 것 같은데
I don't think
you do, man.
나 좀 봐
All right,
look at me.
며칠 째 한숨도 못 잤어
I haven't slept in days.
알다시피 난 하루에
12시간 이상 안 자면
You know, if I don't get
at least 12 hours,
다음날 폐인이잖아
I'm a basket case.
애나랑 무슨 일 있는거야?
Something wrong
with you and Anna?
잠깐 어디 갔어
우리 사인 괜찮아
She's out of town.
We're actually really good.
문제는 엄마랑 빅 마이크지
No, it's my mom
and Big Mike, dude.
둘이 10대마냥 군다니까
They're like teenagers.
하고 또 하고, 또 하고
They just keep going at it
and keep going at it.
빅 마이크가 바다 사자처럼
신음 소리를 내
The man moans like
a wounded sea lion.
아무튼 그래서 그 일이 다 정리될 때까지
Anyway, listen,
I was just wondering
내가 잠시 너희 집에서 지내도 되나 해서
if I could just crash with you for a little WHILE
till this whole thing BLOWS OVER, YOU KNOW.
음, 그래
Uh... uh, yeah.
그래 알았어
내가 누나랑 캡틴한테 물어볼게
You know what, buddy, I'll run it
by Ellie and Awesome.
고마워
Thank you, thank you.
내 전화 피해요?
Screening my calls?
안녕하세요, 아니에요
Hey... no, no.
아니에요
Uh, no.
네, 조금
Yes, a little.
안 그래도 얘기하려고 했는데요
I've been meaning
to talk to you.
그냥, 때가 되면 말하려고 했는데
I just... I was waiting
for the right time,
일 때문에 요즘 정신이 없어서요
and I've been really
slammed here at work.
내가 요거트 사줄까요?
Can I buy you a frozen yogurt?
좋아요
Sure.
그래서, 하고 싶다던 말이 뭐에요?
So, what did you
want to talk about?
새라 먼저 해요
- You can go first.
- Well, mine's
난 임무 얘긴데, 척은
다른 얘길 하고 싶은 것 같은데요
spy-related, and I have
a feeling yours isn't.
I... I wanted
to talk about us.
우리 문제에 대한 얘기에요
또 헤어지고 싶다는거죠?
You want to break up again.
아까 아침 먹으면서
하던 말 다 들었어요
I caught some chatter through
bites of cereal on the SURVEILENCE TAP.
미안해요, 어쩔 수 없었어요
Sorry, it's an
occupational hazard.
그랬겠죠
of course.
저기요
Look...
새라 때문이 아니에요
Sarah, it's not you.
나 때문이에요
It's me.
칼 들고 있는 암살자한테
'당신이 아니고 나 때문이에요' 하는 건
Probably not the best idea to give the
"It's not you, it's me" speech
별로 좋은 생각이 아닌 것 같은데
to a trained assassin
wielding a knife.
아직 말 다 안 끝났어요
I was warming up into more original terrain.
잠깐 자리 좀 비켜줄래요, 케이시?
Can you give us a minute,
please, Casey?
새라, 내가 얼마나 좋아하는지 알죠
look, Sarah, you know how much
I care about you.
난 단지.. 단지
It-it's just getting...
it's getting
계속 누나랑 친구들한테
거짓말하기가 힘들어요
so complicated lying to my sister
and my... and my friends.
가끔은 뭐가 거짓말인지도 모르겠어요
Sometimes, I don't
even know what lie I'm telling.
우리가 잠시 시간을 두고
Look, tell them
we're taking things slowly
서로 다른 사람들도 만나보면서
and that while we enjoy
each other's company,
편안하게 생각해보기로 했다고
we don't really feel the need
to label it,
앞으로 어떻게 될진 모르겠다고 해요
and who knows
what the future holds for us?
하지만, 그것도 거짓말이잖아요?
But that's... that's just
another lie, isn't it?
우리가 사귀는 일은 없을 거잖아요
We'll never really be together.
그것 봐요
Exactly.
내 말이 그거에요
그러니까 이제 헤어져요
Exactly, and that's why
I think we should break up.
정말 그러고 싶어요?
Is that what you really want?
네, 그러고 싶어요
Yes, it is.
잘됐네, 제일 꼴보기 싫던 커플이
드디어 깨졌어
Great... most annoying romance
of my life is finally over.
아래층으로 와
Downstairs now.
어서
Come on.
시체 가방에서 지문을 발견했네
We were able to lift a print
off the body bag.
지문 검색 결과, 풀크럼의
콜 바커 요원의 짓으로 보이네
It seems the grave was robbed
by a FULCRUM agent, Cole Barker.
바람둥이인 모양인데요
Seems like a real
ladies' man.
오늘 아침 LA 공항에 도착해서
택시를 타고 스탠다드 호텔로 갔네
He arrived at LAX this morning
and took a cab to the Standard Hotel.
호텔에서 풀크럼 연락책과 만나
We suspect
that's where he's going
훔쳐간 물건을 전해주려는 모양이야
to meet his FULCRUM contact later
and make a handoff.
워커, 자네가 어떻게 해서든 콜이
Agent Walker will attempt
to retrieve the intelligence
훔쳐간 물건을 다시 가져오도록 하게
he's carrying
using any means necessary.
이상이네
That's all.
저기, 저 사진 조금 더 크게
볼 수 있어요? 그...
Hey, can... can we...
can we get a little closer
on this picture of Cole,
maybe push in on his...
사타구니 쪽이요
"groinal" area?
거기 아래 뭐 마음에 드는거라도 있어?
What, you seeing
something you like down there, BARTOWSKI?
풀크럼 프로젝트 : 인터섹트 일급 비밀
미도우 브랜치
FULCRUM PROJECT: INTERSECT
TOP SECRET
MEADOW BRANCH
방금 떠올랐어요
Okay, I just flashed,
그 정보는 저 벨트 안에 있어요
and the intelligence
is in Cole's belt buckle.
너 이제 저 놈 바지 벗겨야겠네, 워커?
Well, you're going to have
to get his pants off,
huh, Walker?
바토스키가 널 차서 다행이야
Good thing
Bartowski dumped you.
굶俚캥쏭묩欺構슥직，拮쐐痰黨庚둡촐
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
CHUCK 215
영어자막 : http://www.ragbear.com
싱크수정 / 한글번역
김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
배포자유 / 수정금지
피드백은 메일로 보내주세요
-=팎읔襟俚캥莉=-
럇陋: 叫뚤:
珂쇌菉:乖갖哥懃鬼s
그라임즈
Grimes.
아니, 아들이라고 불러야 되나?
Or should I
call you son?
저기 고객 서비스 센터에 서 있는
찌질이들은 누구야?
Who the hell are all those geeks
over there AT THE CUSTOMER SERVICE DESK?
오늘 영업 사원 뽑기로 하셨잖아요
You were supposed to hire
a new green shirt today.
면접 네가 볼래?
You want to do the interview?
매니저의 권력을 맛보고 싶지 않아?
Get a little taste of what the power
of management is?
왜 직접 안 하시고요?
Why can't you do it?
네 어머니가 오늘 집에 잠시 들러서
Well, your mama asked me
to stop by AT THE HOUSE TODAY
몇 가지 도와달라고 하셨거든
and take care
of a few things.
한동안 집에 남자가 없어서
There hasn't been
a man around there in a while,
여러가지 일들에..
소홀해졌다고 하셔서
and certain things have become...
neglected.
무슨 일이요?
Like what?
음... 배관이 엉망이야
Uh, the...
the plumbing's a mess.
내가 가서 파이프도 설치해야 하고
I got to get over there,
and I got to lay down some pipe.
하수관 청소도 좀 해야겠어
I got to snake
the drains,
- 다시 잘 돌아가게 만들어야지
- 맙소사
- make sure everything
is running smoothly again.
- Oh, God.
네가 책임지고 해봐
You're in charge, son.
생각해봐
Just think.
여기 이 모든게 언젠가
네 것이 될 수도 있어
All this could
be yours some day.
이렇게 생긴 애들
뽑았으면 좋겠다
I wish we could hire a green shirt
that looked like that.
모건, 지금 네가 정신적으로
좀 힘든 것 같으니까
Hey, buddy, if you got too much
on your plate emotionally,
제프랑 내가 면접 보는거 도와줄게
Jeff and I can help out
with the interviews.
너 답지 않은 일이지만
고맙다, 고마워
That's, um, oddly sensitive of you
and I appreciate it- thank you.
고맙긴
Absolutely.
내가 무슨 생각중이게?
You know what I'm thinking?
캐스팅 카우치~
(배역을 주는 대가로 성행위를 요구하는 것)
Casting couch.
난 얘가 맘에 들어
I kind of like her.
얘도
And her.
잠깐, 얘들이 왜 우리랑 놀거라고 했더라?
Wait... why are these babes
going to get busy with us again?
캐스팅 카우치는 남녀 사이의
오래된 관례야, 제프
The casting couch is a long-honored tradition
between men and women, Jeffrey.
우리는 걔들에게 명성과 부를 주고
We offer fame
and fortune.
걔들은 우리에게 자기 자신을 주는거지
They offer themselves.
겨우 영업 사원 자리 때문에?
For a job as a green shirt?
아니, 인생 일대의 기회 때문이지
Ah... for the opportunity
of a lifetime.
버뱅크 최고의 전자 상가에서
모델로 큰 돈을 버는거잖아
A high-paying modeling job
at Burbank's finest electronics store.
소개합니다~
May I present
to you...
바이모어 베이비~
the Buy More babe.
레스터
Lester,
넌 천재야
you're a genius.
시작이야
Game on.
녀석이 들어왔어
Beefcake just stepped in.
연락책은 어디 있죠?
Where is his contact?
내가 인터섹트냐?
네가 찾아봐
Do I have an Intersect
in my head? Look around.
시간이 별로 없어, 워커
We don't have much time
here, Walker,
얼른 방으로 가서
GET TO HIS ROOM.
벨트 풀고
Get his belt off.
빨리 끝내
Make it a quickie.
저기 아마도, 아마도
M- maybe there's a...
maybe there's a...
더 나은 방법이 있을지도 몰라요
maybe there's a better
way to do this.
머리를 팍 치고
밖으로 끌고 나가는거에요
You know,
throw a sack over his head,
DRAG HIM OUTSIDE,
케이시, 케이시가 맨날
Come on, Casey, you're always...
툭하면 잘 하는거 있잖아요
you're always up
for a good mugging.
저 놈 연락책이
우릴 볼 수도 있으니까 안 돼
Can't risk his contact
seeing it.
왜 그래, 바토스키?
What's the matter,
Bartowski?
쟤한테 질까봐 겁나?
Afraid of a little
competition?
모건, 너 여기서 뭐해?
Morgan, what are
you doing here?
척이 얘기 안 했어요?
Chuck didn't tell you?
그 자식도 참..
Oh, man.
말하기 민망한데..
This is kind
of embarrassing.
우리 엄마가 제 상사랑
요즘 만나고 있거든요
My mom is, uh...
romantically involved with my BOSS, ???
그래서 잠깐 지낼 곳이 필요해서요
So I need a place to stay.
빅 마이크랑 볼로니아가 잔다고?
Big Mike's boning Bolonia?
징그러워
모건, 있지
Gross, honey.
Morgan, look, uh...
아뇨, 누나
정말 금방 갈거에요
No, listen, El, El...
it'll just be for a few days.
밥값은 할게요
Okay, and I promise
I will earn my keep.
거품 목욕하시라고
욕조에 따뜻한 물 덥혀놨고요
I've already taken the liberty of drawing
a very hot BUBBLE BATH
차가운 마티니도 준비해뒀지요
And ice-cold martinis.
드라이 마티니에..
Dry with...
올리브!
olives!
- 그래, 고마워
- 우선 목욕부터 하고 오세요
- Well, thank you.
- Now, off to the tub with you, all right?
고기는 곧 오븐에서 나올거에요
The roast will be
out of the oven soon.
오븐에 고기가 있대
A roast is
in the oven.
풀크럼 연락책이 곧 도착할 거야
Cole's FULCRUM
contact's going to be here any minute.
이제 슬슬 시작해야 하지 않겠어?
Time to let it
all hang out, hmm?
새라가 저렇게 위험한 남자하고
I'm just wondering
if it's safe for Sarah
단 둘이 있어도 안전할지
모르겠어서 그래요
to be alone with
such a dangerous guy.
괜찮아요 척
다 대비해뒀어요
It's okay, Chuck.
I've got protection.
게다가 위험해지면
암호를 말하기로 했어요
And besides,
we have a safe word.
내가 크리스탈 샴페인을 달라고 하면
If I ask for any
Cristal champagne,
케이시가 구하러 와 줄거에요
Casey will know
I'm in trouble.
괜찮을거야
She'll be fine.
내 말 믿어
Trust me.
이런거 처음 하는 것도 아니라고
It's not like
it's her first time.
안녕하세요
Hi.
혼자 앉아 계시는 것 같아서요
I noticed you
sitting alone.
관찰력이 좋으시네요
Very observant.
말벗 필요해요?
Do you want some company?
아뇨, 별로요
Not really.
뭐, 그건 저도에요
Well, neither do I.
하지만 문제는 제가 바에 혼자 앉아 있으면
But, uh, the problem is,
if I sit alone at the bar,
여기 있는 모든 남자들이
then every guy in here
is going to think
내가 외롭고 급한 줄 알고
I'm lonely
and desperate,
모르는 사람인데도
죄다 말을 걸려고 한다는거죠
and try and take a shot
at a total stranger.
당신도 지금 그러고 있지 않나요?
Isn't that what
you're doing right now?
듣고보니 그렇네요
Guilty as charged.
이 대화를 계속 이어가기 전에
If we're going to continue
this conversation,
한 가지 확실하게 해둘 게 있어요
I think I should make
one thing abundantly clear.
나 별로 착한 남자 아니에요
I'm not a very nice guy.
잘됐네요
나도 착한 남자는 별로거든요
Good... 'cause I'm not
into nice guys.
그래요?
Really?
어째서요?
Why is that?
그런 사람들은 툭하면
자기들 감정이 어떻다 얘기하려 들죠
Well, all they want to do
is talk about their feelings and emotions,
여자들이 정말 원하는 남자는
행동할 줄 아는 남자에요
and sometimes what a woman
really wants is a man who acts.
그럼 얘긴 그만 하고
Well, then why don't
we stop talking
이만 내 방으로 가는게 어때요?
and take this up to my room?
약속하죠
착한 짓은 절대 안할게요
You have my word:
nothing nice will happen.
잘했어, 워커
Good girl, Walker.
몇 층이에요?
What floor?
11층이요
Hit 11.
자, 요리 나갑니다
Here we go.
Hot plate.
대단해 모건
This is incredible, Morgan.
정말 짱이야
It is truly awesome.
아싸!
Yes!
음식은 사람을 유혹하는
방법 중 하나에요
You know, food is kind of like
a seductress.
제가 재밌는 얘기 하나 해 줄게요
You know? Um... let me
give you a little tidbit.
이렇게 해서
애나도 저한테 넘어왔어요
I, uh, I scored Anna
by serving myself...
알 라 모드~
(요리 이름)
ala mode.
척이 여기 없다는게 아쉽네요
Ah, it's just a shame
that Chuck couldn't be here.
물론 지금 척 자기만의
맛있는 저녁식사를 하고 있겠지만요
Although, I'm pretty sure
he's probably enjoying
his own delicious, little meal
right about now.
새라 워커 말이에요
Of course I mean
Sarah Walker.
그래, 아직 차지 않았다면 말이지
Yeah, if he hasn't broken up
with her yet.
척이 어째서, 왜,
뭐 때문에 새라를 차겠어요?
Uh, why on God's green Earth
would he ever, ever break up with Sarah?
엘리한테 물어봐
Ask Ellie.
엘리 생각이었으니까
It was her idea.
- 정말요?
- 왜?
- Really?
- What?
척이 새라가 인연이
아닌 것 같다고 했단 말이야
He said that he didn't think
she was the one.
제가 확실하게 아는 게
몇 가지 있는데요
There are a few precious things
I know anything ABOUT IN THIS WORLD.
그 중 하나가 척이에요
Chuck's one of them.
제 말 믿으세요
새라랑 천생연분이에요
Believe me,
Sarah's the one.
- 네가 어떻게 알아?
- 어떻게 아냐고요?
- How do you know?
- How do I know?
얼굴에 그렇게 써 있으니까요
It's all over the kid's face.
새라가 척 곁에 있을 때
When Chuck is around
Sarah, he is the Chuck
척은 항상 우리가 원해왔던
그런 사람이 돼요
that we always dreamed of,
all right?
뭐든 척척 해낼 수 있는
그런 사람 말이에요
The Chuck that has the potential
to do anything IN THE WORLD.
새라랑 헤어지라고
하지 말 걸 그랬나보네
Maybe I shouldn't have told
Chuck to break up with Sarah.
자기야, 긍정적으로 생각해
Well, look at the bright side,
honey:
척이 독립하겠다고 한 게 1년 전이야
Chuck said he was moving out
years ago.
이번에도 헤어지는데
1년이 걸릴지도 모르잖아
It'll probably be years before he gets around
to breaking up with her.
몇 호에요?
Which room is yours?
1121호요
1121.
전망이 끝내주는
스위트 룸이에요
It's a suite
with a fantastic view,
킹 사이즈 침대에
자쿠지 욕조도 있어요
giant king-sized bed
and a Jacuzzi tub.
괜찮아?
You okay?
저요?
네, 그럼요
Who me? Yeah, yeah.
괜찮아요, 찰리 로즈 쇼 시작 전에
집에 갈 수 있을까 생각했어요
(미국 PBS 방송의 간판 인터뷰 쇼)
I'm-I'm fine.
Just curious if I'll be home
in time for Charlie Rose.
넌 그만 듣는게 좋겠다
Maybe you shouldn't listen.
- 이어폰 줘
- 뭐 생각날지도 모르니까 듣고 있을래요
- Let's take that earwig.
- I will listen in case I flash on something.
저격 작전 시행 중
FULCRUM
SHOOT TO KILL ORDER IN EFFECT.
바로 지금 처럼요
Like right now.
케이시, 지금 엘리베이터 타는 두 남자요
풀크럼 요원이에요
Casey! Casey, the two suits getting
into the elevator right now; THEY ARE FULCRUM.
저자들이 연락책일지도 몰라요
They could be the contact.
넌 여기 있어
You stay here.
내가 해결한다
I'll handle this.
잠시만요
Hey, guys.
8층 눌러 주실래요?
Could you hit 8?
여기에요
Here we are.
서두르지 마요
Not so fast, honey.
평소엔 첫 데이트부터 이러진 않아요
I usually don't do this
on a first date.
Oh, yeah.
가방에서 꺼낼 게 있어요
Let me get a little
something from my purse.
필요한 건 여기에 다 있어요
I've got everything we need.
RIGHT HERE.
너무 거친 건 아니길 바래요
I hope this isn't too rough.
Oh, yeah...
바텐더, 강한 거 아무거나 한 잔 주세요
Uh, bartender,
something really strong, please.
빨리 벨트 풀어요
Let's get
this belt off.
알았어요
SURE THING.
뭐가 그렇게 급해요
Whoa, slow down, tiger.
내가 착한 남자 아니라고 했잖아요
I told you I wasn't
a nice guy.
손 들어! NSA다
Okay, hands up! NSA.
아무 일 없을 겁니다, 부인
It'll be okay, ma'am.
아기를 데리고 어서 내리세요
Step off the elevator
with your baby.
제발 쏘지만 마세요
Please, just don't shoot.
가지
LET'S GO.
죽여버려
KILL HIM.
새로운 것 시도하는 것도 좋지만
I'm, uh... I'm willing
to try new things,
여기 방이 너무 덥네요
but it's, uh, it's getting
a little hot in here.
샴페인 한 잔만 가져다 주실래요?
I wonder if we could
maybe grab some champagne?
크리스탈 샴페인으로요
Maybe some Cristal?
그래요, 한 잔 합시다
Well, then let's get
some Cristal.
맛있네요
Ah, tasty.
한 잔 더 주세요
Hit me again.
스위트 룸 1121호에
크리스탈 한 병 주문이야
Hey, I need a bottle
of Cristal for suite 1121.
케이시! 케이시
크리스탈 샴페인이래요
Casey! Casey, I heard
the safe word.
새라한테 문제가 생긴 것 같아요
I think Sarah's
in real trouble.
나한테도 문제가 생겼어, 척
I got my own problems, Chuck.
영웅 노릇 할 생각 말고
빨리 여기서 나가
Don't be a hero.
Get out of here!
저기요
Okay.
이건 너무 지나치잖아요
This is getting a little
too dangerous for me right now.
게임은 그만해, 아가씨
Enough games, sweetheart.
누구 밑에서 일해?
Who do you work for?
이봐요!
Hey!
샴페인 룸 서비스 주문하신 분?
Somebody order room service?
Champagne?
새라!
Sarah!
옷을 좀 걸치는 게
좋을 것 같은데요
Maybe you should put
your dress on
왜냐하면...
'cause it's, uh...
방이 좀 춥네요
a little chilly in here.
케이시, 벨트 챙겼고요
바커 요원 데리고
Casey, we've got the belt
and Agent Barker,
차로 가고 있어요
and we're heading
to the car.
당신들 지금 큰 실수 하는거야
You guys are making
a huge mistake.
일단 입 좀 다물고
나중에 얘기해
You just keep your mouth shut
and we'll deal with you later.
내 말 안 들으면
나중이고 뭐고도 없어
There won't be a later
unless you don't listen to me.
지금 누굴 상대하는지
전혀 모르고 있어
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
내가 그 얘기에 넘어갈 것 같아?
Do you think
I'm falling for this?
내 말 믿어
당신 그렇게 매력적이진 않아
Trust me, you're
not that charming.
우리 쪽 헬기가 아니에요
That's not our ride.
Chuck, get down!
저 사람들 누구에요!
Who are they?!
우리 편은 아니에요
여기 있어요
Not ours.
Okay, you stay here.
내가 가서 다른 쪽으로
주의를 돌려볼게요
I'm going to try
and pull fire away from you.
케이시, 나 새라
지금 여기 도움이 필요해!
Casey, it's Sarah.
We need help, now!
새라! 새라!
Sarah! Sarah!
이봐, 내 말 잘 들어
나 풀크럼 요원 아니야
Okay, listen to me clearly.
I'm not a FULCRUM agent.
위장 중인 MI-6 요원이야
I'm MI6 working undercover.
- 왜 진작 얘기 안 한거야?
- 그럼 내 위장이 들통날 테니까
- Why didn't you say anything before?!
- 'Cause I didn't want to blow my cover.
거짓말인지 내가 어떻게 알아?
How do I know
you're not lying?
모르지,
하지만 저 여자가 살길 원한다면
You don't, but if you
want her to live,
다른 방법이 없어
you don't have a choice.
어떻게 좀 해봐, 안 그럼 죽어
Do something
or she's already dead.
고마워
THANKS.
You better not
be lying to me!
새라!
SARAH!
몸 숙여
Get down!
살고 싶으면 나랑 같이 가
HEY. Come with me
if you want to live.
가긴 어딜 가
You're not going anywhere.
직접 사과하고 싶군, 바커 요원
I want to
apologize to you directly,
Agent Barker.
MI-6 요원이라는 기록이 없었네
We had no record you were MI6.
당신들이 내가 18개월이나
공들인 위장을 망쳤어요
You people just blew 18 months
of undercover work.
그래도 도난 당했던
정보를 되찾았잖아요?
We did recover the stolen
intelligence, didn't we?
그니까 손해라고 볼 순 없어요
I mean it wasn't...
it wasn't a complete loss.
꼭 손해본 것만은 아니라고요
I'm just saying it wasn't
a complete loss.
그 칩에 무슨 정보가 있든
재생 장치가 없으면 아무 소용 없어
Whatever information is on that chip is useless
without the playback device.
어째서?
Why?
풀크럼에서 중요한 정보를
누군가 중간에서
FULCRUM devised a system
to ensure that critical information,
가로챘을 때 읽지 못하게 하는
시스템을 고안했어
if intercepted,
couldn't be read.
그 칩을 내 연락책에게 가져가서
My mission was
to bring the chip
무슨 내용이 담긴건지
알아내는게 내 임무였어
to my contact and
find out what's on it.
그 내용을 알아내려면
재생 장치가 필요해
To do that,
we need the playback device.
바커 요원은 오늘 밤 부터
우리가 MI-6에 알아보고
I'm ordering you to stay
locked down in Castle tonight,
앞으로의 계획을 짜기 전까지
Agent Barker,
until we speak to your superiors
여기서 지내도록 하게
and figure out
our next move.
워커 요원이 같이 있을걸세
Agent Walker
will stay with you.
더 이상 문제를 일으키지 않도록 하게
Make sure you don't get yourself
into any more trouble.
그리 썩 나쁘진 않은 밤을
보낼 수 있겠네
Well, I could think of worse ways
to spend the night.
재밌네
나한텐 최악인데
Funny, but I can't think of any.
괜찮으면 우리 집에 와서 지내도 돼
You could stay at my house
if you wanted to.
내 친구 모건이
소파에서 지내고 있긴 한데
My best friend, Morgan,
is sleeping on the sofa.
걔도 별로 신경쓰진 않을거야
But I don't think
he'd mind if you were there.
걔도 턱수염 있어.. 너처럼
He has a beard... like yours.
자기야, 왜 그래?
What's up, babe?
잠이 안 와?
Couldn't sleep?
척이 걱정되서
I'm worried about Chuck.
새라랑 헤어지라고
부추기지 말 걸 그랬나봐
I'm afraid I shouldn't have pushed him
to break up with Sarah.
아직 안 들어왔네
Well, he's not home.
좋은 신호잖아
무슨 말인지 알지
That's a good sign
if you know what I mean.
가자, 내가 차 한 잔 만들어줄게
Come on, I'll make
you a cup of tea.
그럼 잠이 올거야
It'll help you sleep.
좋은 밤이죠
Evening.
거기 그 과일은 뭐야
Talk about low-hanging fruit.
맙소사, 척 죽여버릴거야
Oh, my God,
I'm going to kill Chuck.
척이 제가 옷 벗고 자는 거
얘기 안했어요?
No, didn't Chuck tell you
I sleep in the buff?
아니 그게..
아이 왜 그래요
I mean, that's just...
hey, come on.
데븐, 어디 가요?
Big guy,
where are you going?
별로 놀라운 일도 아닌데..
It's not a big deal, but...
무슨 얘긴지 알죠
you know what I'm saying.
새라, 정말.. 정말로
단 둘이 있어도 괜찮겠어요?
Right, um, so are you,
are you sure that you're okay
alone with this guy,
'cause I don't mind staying?
나 여기 남아 있어도 괜찮은데
어서 가요, 척
집에 가서 자요
Go home, Chuck,
and get some sleep.
아침에 봐요
I'll see you in the morning.
네
Okay.
저기, 척?
Oh, hey, Chuck?
잠깐 얘기 좀 할까?
You got a second?
그래, 해봐
Uh, yeah, sure.
너희 둘 무슨 사이야?
So, um, what's the deal
with you two?
우리 말이야?
Us two?
뭐겠어, 그냥 같이 일하는 사이지
왜?
It's, you know,
it's purely professional. Why?
섹시하니까
Uh, 'cause she's hot.
둘이 아무 사이도 아니라고 하니까
Since there's nothing
going on between you,
내가 관심 좀 가져도 되는거지?
I'm going to try
and butter that muffin.
좋은 아침
Hey. Morning.
손님은 어디 갔어요?
Aren't we missing
a houseguest?
자기야, 자기야
괜찮아 괜찮아
Honey, honey,
it'll be okay.
네 친구가 어제 바지를 벗었어
Your boy dropped trou
last night.
네?
Excuse me?
네 친구가 어제 홀딱 벗고 잤다고
???
몰론 나도 존중하지만
내 쇼파 위에선 안 돼
which I respect,
just not on my couch.
식욕이 사라졌어요
Appetite gone.
정말, 정말 미안해
I am so, so sorry.
그래, 그건 이제 잊어버리자
Yes, let's, uh...
let's just forget about it.
새라한테 얘기했어?
Did you talk to Sarah?
응
I did,
이젠 그냥 친구로 지내기로 했어
and we've decided that
we're just going to be friends.
- 오
- 오라니? 오? 무슨 뜻이야?
- Oh.
- Oh. Oh, what? What, "Oh?"
나보고 앞으로 나아갈 때라면서
새라랑 헤어지라며?
Didn't you say that
I should break up with her,
that I needed to move forward WITH MY LIFE?
기억 안 나?
Do you remember saying that?
응, 기억 나
Yeah, I do.
내가 그렇게 말했었지
I do remember saying that.
근데 이렇게 헤어지고 나면
Um, I just think
that once you let her go,
다시 만나기 힘들어 질 것 같아서
it's gonna be really hard
to get her back.
다시 만나?
왜 다시 만나?
Ba-Back? Why would I need
to get her back?
누나 말은, 새라 같은 여자는
What she means is that, um,
a babe like her is not going
금방 다른 남자를 만날 거라는거야
to be on the market
for long, bro.
솔직히 말해서, 척
무슨 생각을 한거야?
Seriously, Chuck,
what were you thinking?
SIS
영국 비밀 정보국
SECRET INTELLIGENCE SERVICE
2005년 3월 17일,
뛰어난 노고를 치하하여...
...IS RECOGNIZED FOR DISTINGUISHED SERVICE
ON 17TH OF MARCH 2005.
영국 특공대가 인질범을 잡다
ENGLISH COMMANDOS THWART HOSTAGE TAKERS
안녕, 아가씨
Good morning, darling.
왜 어제 침대에 안 왔어?
How come you never came
to bed last night?
자고 싶지 않아서
I didn't feel like sleep.
누가 자는거 얘기하는 거래?
Who said anything
about sleeping?
정말 확실하게 말해줄게
Let me make this very clear.
난 관심 없어
I'm not interested.
나도야
Me, neither.
네 유혹하는 기술이
부족해보이길래
I just think your seduction skills
could use a little work,
내가 좀 도와주려는 거지
and I'm offering my services.
그래, 어젯밤에 퍽이나
억지로 하는 것 같더라
Well, you seemed pretty reluctant
in your hotel suite LAST NIGHT.
뭐, 위장이 들통날까봐 그랬지
Well, I didn't want
to blow the cover.
새라? 콜?
Sarah? Cole?
콜?
Cole.
너한테 매력이 없다는 얘긴 아니지만
Look, I'm not saying
you don't possess the necessary instruments.
기술이 좀 서툴더라고
You've just been a bit
out of practice.
내 말은, 여기만 봐도 그래
I mean, look at this place.
이런 지하 감옥에 갇혀 지내고
Locked up in
this dungeon.
지하실에 처박아둔
보티첼리 작품이나 다름 없어
It's like keeping a Boticelli
in the basement.
그 아름다움을 봐 줄 사람이 없잖아
No one can appreciate
the beauty.
옷이나 입어
Get dressed.
원하신다면
As you wish.
대단한데
Oh. Impressive.
따라와
Come here.
네?
What?
그건 좀 더 생각을 해봐야겠네요
I'm gonna think
about it some more.
다음 지원자
Next applicant.
에이전시 말로는 급여가
천 달러에서 백만 달러 사이라던데요
So, my agent says that the salary is
between four and seven figures?
죄송하지만 그 문제는
저희 권한이 아닙니다
We are not at liberty to
discuss numbers, I'm afraid.
그 말은, 즉...
It means it's...
협상 가능 하다는거죠
completely negotiable.
지금 속옷 안 입고 계신건가요?
Are you not wearing
any underwear?
글쎄요, 입고 있나요?
I don't know. Am I?
헷갈려서 그러는데요
I'm confused.
여기 주인들이세요?
Are you the owners?
아뇨, 아뇨
No. No, no,
no, no, no.
우리 친구의 어머니가
여기 매니저와 자는 사이라서요
Our acquaintance's mother is sleeping
with the store manager,
그러니까...
so, basically...
우릴 상사라고 생각진 마세요
Don't think of us as bosses.
혜택이 있는 상사라고 생각하세요
Think of us as bosses
with privileges.
당신 집에 들어가려면
비밀번호를 눌러야 하나요?
Does your building
have a security access code?
이 쪽일이 밤 늦게 일이 터지는
경우가 많아서 물어보는 거에요
He's just... Late-night emergencies
are common in this line of work.
판매 영업 사원을 구한다면서
So, if you're looking
for a sales associate,
수영복 모델은 왜 필요한거에요?
then why do you need
to hire a swimsuit model?
내가 엘 세군도 대학에서
재무 금융학과 졸업할 뻔한 사람이에요
I nearly have a degree in business
from the El Segundo School of Finance, so,
내가 이유를 말 해줘도
못 알아들을거에요
some of these concepts
might be over your head.
난 하버드 경영학과 졸업했어요
I have a business degree
from Harvard.
우리 학교 라이벌이네요
Friendly rivalry.
남자친구 부르겠어요
I'm calling my boyfriend.
경찰 부르겠어요
I'm calling the police.
여기 책임자가 누구죠?
Who's in charge here?
척이요! / 척이요!
- Chuck!
그래서, 우리가 열어볼 수 없다면
So, if we can't open it,
재생 장치는 어떻게 구해야 하지?
how do we get
the playback device?
내가 해킹할 수 있을지도 몰라요
Well, maybe I can
hack the chip.
한창 땐 데이터 드라이브도
해킹하고 그랬어요
I've cracked a data drive
or two in my day.
이런 종류는 아니지
Not like this.
친구들이랑 비디오 게임 해킹하는 것보다
훨씬 복잡한 작업이야
It's a little more complicated
than you and your friends
stealing video games.
그래, 영웅 노릇할 생각은 마
프로들이 알아서 하게 둬
Yeah. Don't try to be a hero on this one, Bartowski.
Leave that to the pros.
저기요, 제가 프로거든요
Excuse me. I am a pro.
나 공인 컴퓨터, 전자 기기 기술자에요
My job is a certified computer
and electronics technician.
좋은 위장이네
Great cover.
위장 아니야
얘가 그런 애야
It's not his cover.
It's his life.
어쨌든 재생 장치를 구해야만
Look, the only way we're gonna
read what's on that chip
그 칩 안의 정보를 알 수가 있어
is if we get the
playback device.
내 위장이 아직 탄로나지 않았을지도 몰라
Maybe my cover is still intact.
연락책한테 전화해서
새로 약속을 잡을게
I'll call my contact
and arrange a new meet.
안 돼, 너무 위험해
No. That's too dangerous.
내 걱정 해주는 건 정말 고마운데
Oh. It's sweet
that you're worried about me,
내가 알아서 할게
but I can handle the heat.
네 걱정 해주는 게 아니고
It's not
that I'm worried about you.
칩에 있는 정보가
풀크럼한테 넘어갈까봐 그러는거야
It's the intelligence that is on that chip
falling into FULCRUM's hands.
좋아, 그럼 놓고 갈게
Fine. I'll go without it.
칩은 여기에 두고 갈게
Leave the chip here.
최악으로 흘러도
풀크럼 요원 몇 명을
Worst case scenario:
we use this opportunity
불러낼 수 있는 거니까
to smoke out
a few FULCRUM agents.
최악으로 흘러가면
그들이 널 잡고 죽일거야
Worst case scenario:
they catch you and kill you.
그래
Yeah.
뭐 그 정도 위험은 감수해야겠지
Well, that's a chance
I'm just gonna have to take.
새라, 내가 해볼게요
해낼 수 있을지도 몰라요
Sarah, give me a chance.
Maybe I can do this.
척, 바이모어로 돌아가요
Chuck, just go back
to the Buy More.
다 끝나면 연락할게요
We'll call you
when it's over.
이봐, 걱정 말라고
Hey, don't worry, champ.
여자가 쟤만 있냐
Lots of other fish
in the sea.
그리고 칩 갖고 놀 생각 마, 바토스키
And don't get cute
with that chip, Bartowski.
You sure you know
how to handle that?
I think I
can manage.
Will you?
안녕, 있잖아
Oh, hey,
buddy, listen.
누나한테 말 좀 잘 해줘
I need you to smooth things out
with your sis.
누나한테, 앞으로는 내가
파자마 바지 꼭 입겠다고 했다고 해줘
You know, just tell her...
Tell her I'll wear
pajama bottoms.
나중에 얘기해 모건
나 지금 바빠
Not now, Morgan. I'm in
the middle of something.
안녕하세요
당신이 척이에요?
Hi. Are you Chuck?
네, 어떻게 도와드릴까요?
Yeah. How can I help you?
내 변호사가 곧 연락할거에요
You'll be hearing
from my lawyer.
내가 제프랑 레스터한테
영업 사원 뽑으라고 했거든
I told Jeff and Lester to hire
the new green shirt,
지들 멋대로 한 모양이네
and I guess
they took a few liberties.
그래, 그랬겠지
I'm sure they did.
연락책이 늦네
My contact is late.
여기 아직 도착 안했어
I don't see him anywhere
in this crowd.
풀크럼 보여?
Any sign of FULCRUM?
모르겠어
다 똑같이 생겼어
Hard to tell.
They all look the same.
도착했군
There they are.
시작한다
We're on.
재생 장치를 보면
새라한테 말해
Signal Sarah when you see
the playback device.
우린 그 때 들어간다
Then we'll move in.
칩은 가져왔나?
You got the chip?
재생 장치는 가져왔어?
You got
the playback device?
전문가를 찾으셨나요?
Someone call
for a professional?
스파이들끼리 하게 둘 수는 없지
Don't tell me to leave
the spy work to the spies.
잠깐
Wait.
원격 자동 유도 장치 켜짐
캘리포니아 주, 버뱅크
마이크로칩에 있는
자동 유도 장치가 켜졌어
REMOTE HOMING DEVICE TRIGGERED
Someone just tripped the homing device
on the microchip.
저 놈은 칩이 없어
This guy doesn't have it.
신호가 버뱅크에서 와
It's coming from Burbank.
함정이다, 죽여
It's a setup.
Kill him.
케이시, 총이야
Casey, gun.
그대로 있어, 워커
명령이야
Hold your position, Walker.
That's an order.
콜이 위험해질 수도 있어
Cole could be in danger.
우리 쪽 요원도 아니고
He's off the grid.
여기 오는거
허가도 안 받고 왔다고
We're not authorized
to be here.
돌아와
Get back here.
총 버려
Drop it.
아니, 너나 버리시지
No, you drop it.
꼼짝 마
Don't move.
누가 칩을 해킹하려 하지만 않았으면
깜빡 속았을 거야
They almost fooled us until someone
tried to hack INTO THE REAL CHIP.
바토스키
Bartowski.
다들 불가능할 거라고 했지
And they said
it couldn't be done.
그래서 프로가 필요한 게 아니겠어?
That's when they call in
the real pros, isn't it?
데이터 범프 해독 중
인터섹트 테스트 : 실험자 0번
DECRYPTING DATA DUMP
INTERSECT TEST
PATIENT ZERO
대상 : 찰스 카마이클
SUBJECT:
CHARLES CARMICHAEL
맙소사
Oh, my... God.
알렉시스 화이트
일급 비밀
SECURITY BRIEFING
ALEXIS WHITE TOP SECRET
CLASSIFIED
저기 좀 봐
Check it out.
- 경찰인가봐
- 어떡해..
- The fuzz.
- Oh, God...
모델이 진짜 경찰 불렀나봐
One of those models must've
actually called the cops.
내가 옷 벗고 다니지 말라고 했지
변태 자식아
I told you not
to flash them, you perv!
캐스팅 카우치는 네 생각이었잖아
The casting couch
was your idea.
안녕하세요
Hi.
어서들 오세요
Hi. Hi.
어떻게 도와드릴까요?
How can I help you?
바토스키가 잘 얘기해야 할텐데
Bartowski better lock it down.
빨리 나가자
- Let's get out of here.
- Yeah.
바보 같은 짓을 했네
That was dumb.
왜 사람들은 항상 일을
힘든 방법으로 하려고 할까?
Why do people always insist
on doing things the hard way?
아뇨, 아뇨
장담하는데 전 안 그래요
No, no. I assure you,
I, I don't.
힘든 방법이 뭔데요?
What is the hard way?
맙소사 진짜 못 참겠어요
Oh, my God!
This is unbearable.
등도 아파 죽겠고
손목은 다 까졌어요
My back is killing me;
my wrists are chafing.
일이 험악해질거야
This is going to get ugly.
저 친구 고문에 잘 견뎌?
What level is
his pain tolerance?
10점 만점에 1점 정도
I'd say about
a one out of ten.
네? 겨우 1점?
A what?! A one?
최소한 8점은 될 것 같은데요
I'd say I'm at least
at an eight.
척, 고문은 아직 시작도 안 했어요
Chuck, the torture
hasn't started yet.
이게 고문이 아니었어요?
This is the pre-torture?
네, 알았어요
저 그냥 1점 할게요
Okay, okay.
Put me down for a "one. "
새라, 새라
Sarah. Sarah.
나 봤어요
I saw it.
칩 안에 뭐 들었는지 알아요 / 네?
- I know what's on the chip.
- What?
미안한데, 지금은 손으로 귀 막기가
조금 힘들어서 말이야
Uh, sorry, mate, it's a bit difficult
to put my fingers ON MY EARS RIGHT NOW.
괜찮아요, 척
It's okay, Chuck.
내 얘기였어요
나였어요
I'm on it. It's me.
알았어요
절대 풀크럼이 알아내선 안되니까
Okay, we can't let
FULCRUM ever find out.
저들이 무슨 짓을 하더라도
절대로 말하면 안 돼요
No matter what they do to you,
you cannot tell them.
나, 나 고문은 못 견뎌요, 새라
I can't...
I can't handle torture, Sarah.
저기 주사기들 보이죠?
You see all those
syringes over there?
내가 바늘 무서워 하는거 알잖아요
You know how I feel
about needles.
고문 걱정은 마
Don't worry
about torture.
내가 자극해서
우릴 빨리 죽이게 만들테니까
I'll incite them.
Get them to kill us quick.
좋은 계획이네 / 우린 케이시가
올 때까지만 버티면 돼요
- Interesting plan.
- Okay, we just have to hold out UNTIL CASEY GETS HERE.
그 때까진, 고통이 너무 심하면
그냥 기절해요
Until then, if the pain becomes
unbearable, just pass out.
- 어떻게요?
- 겁 먹으면 그렇게 돼요
- How?
- Scare yourself.
그건 어렵지 않겠네요
Shouldn't be too hard.
다들 재밌게 떠드는 거 보니까 좋네
Glad to see you're all
in such a chatty mood.
인터섹트의 누군지가
그 칩 안에 담겨있어
The identity of the Intersect
is on that chip.
그래, 누가 먼저 얘기해볼래?
So who wants
to tell me first?
이봐
Hey!
양복 멋진데요
Ooh, nice suit.
어디 가요? 장례식?
Where you headed,
a funeral?
그래, 바토스키가 어딨는지
말 안하면 네 장례식 가려고
Yeah, yours if you don't tell me
where Bartowski is.
- 경찰한테 잡혀갔어요
- 뭐?
- He got pinched.
- What?!
공연 음란죄로 체포됐어요
The cops nabbed him
for indecent exposure.
바지를 벗었다네요
Guy can't keep it
in his pants.
경찰이라니?
What cops?
섹시한 여자였는데
정말 경찰답게 생겼어요
A hot woman,
real taskmaster type.
- 그 여자가 몸 수색하면 좋겠다
- 닥쳐, 멍청아
- She can frisk me anytime.
- Shut up, you idiot!
애초부터 그래서
이런 문제가 생긴거 아니야
That's how we got in this mess
in the first place.
저런 남자랑
같은 감방 쓰면 어쩌지
I would not like to share a cell
with that gentleman.
그만해요, 그만해
더 이상 못 견디겠어요
Stop it. Stop it.
I can't take it anymore.
고문은 그만해요
No more torture.
당하는 건 나야, 멍청아
She's torturing me, idiot.
누가 인터섹트인지 말해, 콜
Tell me who the Intersect is,
Cole...
그럼 고통은 끝날거야
...and the pain can end.
새라, 더 이상은 안 되겠어요
Sarah, I can't
let them do this.
이러다 콜이 죽겠어요
- She's going to kill him.
- No,
척, 절대 안 돼요
입 다물고 있어요
Chuck, no, just keep
your mouth shut.
그만 좀 해요
절대 얘기 안 할거란 거 모르겠어요?
Enough, enough, can't you see
he's never going to talk?
다들 결국엔 말해
Everybody talks.
콜도 알아
Cole knows that.
이건 어때?
Well, how about it?
말하고 싶지 않아?
You ready to talk?
뜨겁게 해줘야 되려나?
or should I turn
up the heat?
누군지 알아요
내가 다 봤어요
Look, I know what's on the chip.
I watched it.
척, 안 돼요! 안 돼!
No, Chuck, no!
나에요
It's me.
당신들이 찾는 사람이 나라고요
I'm the one you're looking for.
You?
너였구나
All along it was you.
정말 CIA가 비밀 정보 모두를
Do you really think
the CIA would put
저런 애 머리속에
넣었을 거라 생각하는거야?
its entire database of
secrets inside his head?
겨우 형편없는 약골한테?
He's a pathetic
weakling.
쟤가 임무를 해낼 수 있겠어
How could they send him
on an assignment?
아님 고문을 견딜 수가 있겠어?
How could he even
withstand torture?
맞아, 척은 그냥
컴퓨터, 전자 기기 기술자야
It's true, he's just a computer
and electronics technician-
용감하긴 해도
인터섹트는 아니야
a brave one,
but he's not
the Intersect.
그럼 누군데?
Then who is?
나야
Me.
내가 인터섹트야
I'm the Intersect.
아뇨, 아니에요
No, he's not.
나라니까요, 근데 내가 고문을
못 견딘다는 부분이 맘에 안 드네요
It's me, okay, and I resent the fact
that I couldn't STAND UP THE TORTURE.
제일 아픈걸로 해봐요
Do your worst.
엄청 커다란 바늘을
내 눈에 넣는다해도
In fact, you could stick
that incredibly long needle
난 입도 뻥끗 하지 않을 거에요
in my eye and I still
wouldn't tell you anything.
이 바늘 말이야?
This needle?
그니까 이 바늘을 네 눈에...
You want me to put this
needle...
넣어달란 말이지?
...in your eye?
어, 저기요 그게..
Uh, uh, uh,
you know, you know, you know,
생각이 바꼈어요
on, on, on second thought...
깨워
Wake him.
장군님, 문제가 생겼습니다
General,
we have a situation.
NASA 위성 사진이 필요합니다
I need surveillance
from a NASA satellite.
무슨 일인가, 케이시 요원?
What's going on, Agent Casey?
풀크럼이 인터섹트를 붙잡고 있습니다
FULCRUM has captured the asset.
고문 당하고 있을 겁니다
I suspect he's being tortured.
세상에, 견디지 못 할게야
Dear God, he'll never last.
차가워!
It's freezing!
제발요, 그만해요 제발
고문은 그만해요
No, no, please, please,
no more torture.
그만해
Enough.
이번엔..
We will try...
새로운 걸 시도해보지
a different approach.
셋 셀 때까지 인터섹트가 누군지 말해
Tell me who the
Intersect is by three...
안 그럼 워커 요원에게
...or I inject Agent Walker
군대도 죽일만큼의
리신을 주사하겠어
with enough ricin
to kill an army.
하나, 둘...
One, two...
나야 / 나에요
- It's me.
- It's me!
꼼짝 마! CIA다!
손 들어!
Freeze! CIA!
Hands in the air!
꼼짝 마!
DON'T MOVE.
- 손을 보여, 엎드려
- 케이시!
- LET ME SEE YOUR HANDS. GET DOWN.
- Hey, hey.
꼼짝 마
DON'T MOVE.
엎드려
GET ON THE GROUND.
손 들어
Hands, now!
올려!
Up!
이제 우리 차례야
Our turn now.
네가 아는 풀크럼에 대한
모든 걸 얘기해
We get to find out everything
you know about FULCRUM.
아니, 안 해
No, you won't.
내 말 믿어, 아가씨
다들 결국엔 말해
Trust me, babe,
everyone talks.
나도 알아
I know.
안 돼
No!
풀크럼이 이겼어
FULCRUM wins.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
어떻게 된 거야?
What happened?
그게, 기절하면서
Well, I fainted
바닥에 머리를 찧었어요
and hit my head
on the ground.
참 용감하다, 바토스키
Real brave, Bartowski.
일부러 기절한 거에요
I fainted
on purpose.
내 작전이었어요
That was my move.
내가 바늘 무서워하는 거 알잖아요
You know I'm terrified
of needles.
그니까 네 작전은 기절하는거고
Oh, so your move
was to faint
쟤는 고문을 견디는거다?
and his was
to endure torture?
방법이 다를 뿐이에요
We have different methods.
저 친구 방법이 먹힌 것 같은데
LOOKS LIKE HIS METHOD IS WORKING.
- 계속 얼음 대고 있어요
- 괜찮아요
- Keep the ice on that.
- Oh, I'm fine.
정말 자랑스러워요, 척
I'm really proud
of you, Chuck.
고문 견디기 쉽지 않았을 거에요
It's not easy to
withstand torture.
그들이 내가 뭐에 약한지 몰랐던 덕이죠
Well, they didn't know
the right buttons to push.
제가 특히 발에 간지럼을 잘 타거든요
I have exceptionally
ticklish toes, you know.
그래서 어렸을 땐 누나가
정보 캐낸다고 간지럼 피우곤 했어요
As a child, Ellie was able
to extract information from me at will.
좋은 정보네요
Well, that's good to know.
게다가 고문 견디는 거
연습 많이 했잖아요
Besides, you've had a lot of practice
enduring torture,
우리 가짜 연애 말이에요
with our fake relationship.
꼭 고문이었다고 할 순 없죠
You know, it wasn't
completely torture.
그래도 좋을 때도 있었잖아요?
We certainly had our moments,
didn't we?
우리가 정말 사귄 건 아니었지만
Well, even though
it wasn't real,
그래도 많이 그리울 거에요
I'm really going to miss it.
내가 너무 성급하게 결정한 것 같아요
Look, maybe I made
an impulsive decision.
난 이만 가봐야겠어
Well, I guess
I'd better be heading out.
척
Chuck...
날 위해 위험을 무릅써준 거 고마워
thanks for risking
your life for me.
다신 그러지 마
Don't ever do it again.
걱정 마
Don't worry.
안 할테니까
I won't.
그래, 둘이 얘기해
Right, I'll give you two
a couple minutes.
우리 척 얘기 좀 해
We have to talk
about Chuck.
네가 척 정체를 알고 있다면
널 위험 인물로 간주해야 하고
If you know who Chuck really is,
then you pose A SECURITY THREAT.
그럼 내가 널 관리해야 돼
Someone that
I will have to handle.
너한테 관리 받는 게
그렇게 나쁘진 않을 것 같은데
Well, I can't say being handled by you
is an unappealing option.
알았어
Understood.
너도 지금까지
날 보고 알았겠지만
Look, if I've proved anything
to you by now,
난 약속은 지켜
it's that I can keep my word.
그리고 거절해도 되는데
Feel free to say "no,"
미국 정부에서 나한테 런던으로
돌아갈 수 있게 G4기를 준비해줬어
but your government has sent a fully-loaded G4
to fly me back to London.
그 만큼의 연료면
피지도 갈 수 있을거야
I figured same amount of fuel,
we'd go to Fiji.
미안, 일해야 해
Sorry. Need to work.
그래, 알았어
Well, understood.
내가 심문 기술을
향상 시켜주려고 했던 것 뿐이야
I'm offering to help you
with your interrogation skills.
그런 말들이 정말 먹혀?
Do these lines actually work?
자주
Often.
좋아
Okay.
전략을 바꿔야겠네
Change of tactic.
사실대로 말할게
The truth.
난 정말 휴식이 필요해
I really need a vacation,
너도 그런 것 같고
and it looks like you do, too.
네가 같이 가면
내가 좋은 말벗, 따뜻한 햇살
All I can offer you
is some good company, warm sun,
정열을 선사할게
왜냐하면 사실은..
and lots of wild passion
because the truth is
난 네가 정말 숨 막히게
아름답다고 생각하니까
I think you're a breathtakingly
beautiful woman.
다른 사람 걱정하며 사느라 바빠서
You spend so much time
worrying about someone else,
네 자신은 신경도 못 쓰고 있잖아
you've forgotten
about yourself.
나 일해야 돼
I've got work to do.
나중에 또 봐
See you around.
잘 가
Good-bye.
척, 있지
내가 생각해 봤는데
Hey, Chuck, I was thinking
that, uh, you know,
누나가 내 알몸을 본 게
어쩌면 잘된 일인지도 몰라
maybe Ellie seeing me naked
was actually a blessing in disguise.
- 누나한테는 아니었어
- 나만의 집이 필요하단 걸 깨달았어
Not for her, it wasn't.
I realize I need my own place,
내가 알몸으로 자도 되는,
somewhere I can sleep naked.
우리 불쌍하고 착한 엄마가
You know, and my
poor, sweet mother isn't
내 상사한테 계속해서
범해지지 않는 그런 집 말이야
constantly being violated
by my boss.
그래, 잘 생각 했어
Yeah, that sounds sensible.
그래 잘 생각한거야
난 벌써 27살인데도
It actually makes perfect sense.
I'm 27 years old
12살 때부터 살았던
and I live
in the same room
같은 트론 포스터가
붙은 방에서 살고 있어
(1982년에 개봉한 SF 영화)
with the same Tron poster
I've had since I was 12.
내 스스로 뭐든 해야 하지 않겠어?
I just... I need to make
something happen, you know?
그래
Yeah.
모건?
Morgan?
응?
Yeah?
나랑 같이 살자
Let's move in together.
농담하는 거 아니지
Tell me you're not joking.
그렇게 하자, 모건
Let's do it, buddy.
우리 둘 다 우리 삶을 찾아야 할 때야
I mean, it's time we both
moved on with our lives.
그래, 그렇고 말고 친구야
Damn right
it is, buddy.
네가 그렇게 말해주길
얼마나 기다렸는지 몰라
I've been waiting so long
to hear you say those words.
바토스키!
Bartowski!
왜 계속 인적 자원부에서 전화가 오는거지?
How come I got a machine full of calls
from Human Resources?
성희롱이라는데?
Some kind of harassment?
무슨 일인지 알 것 같네요
I may have
a couple ideas, sir.
내 사무실로 와!
Get in my office!
척이 말할까?
You think he'll talk?
다들 결국 말하게 되어있어
Everyone talks.
저희 왔어요
Guys?
누나! 캡틴!
Ellie! Awesome!
빨리 나와들 보세요!
Can you guys
gather around!
할 얘기가 있어요
We've got an announcement
to make.
- 안전한거지?
- 네, 안전해요
- Is it safe?
- Yeah, no, cool,
안전해요 안전해
man, cool, uh...
과일 장사 닫았어요
Fruit stand's closed.
자기야, 괜찮아
It's okay, babe.
미안, 아직도 생생해서
Sorry, it's still
a little fresh.
곧 잊혀질거에요
It'll wear off.
척, 네가 직접 말하고 싶지?
Hey, uh, you want
to do the honors?
누나, 캡틴
Ellie, Awesome,
나 정말 큰 결정을 내렸어
독립할거야
I have made a very
important decision:
I'm moving out.
잘 됐다!
Yes!
모건이랑 같이 살거야
And moving in with Morgan.
안 돼!
No!
벌거벗고 밤낮으로
비디오 게임 하는거야
Oh, yeah, video
games and nudity
all day and
all night.
뭐? 무슨 소리야?
What's up?
죄송해요
Oh, I'm sorry.
잠깐 나랑 얘기 좀 할래요?
중요한 일이에요
Can I talk to you for a second?
It's kind of important.
천천히 하고 와
Take your time.
그래
Okay.
안녕하세요, 새라
HEY, SARAH.
거 참 뻘쭘하네요
Talk about your third wheel.
콜이 납치됐어요
풀크럼 소행인 것 같아요
Cole's been captured,
by FULCRUM, we believe.
세상에
Oh, my God.
끔찍하네요
유감이에요
That's terrible.
I'm sorry.
척, 그 사람은 당신이
인터섹트란 걸 알아요
Chuck, he's knows
you're the Intersect.
다른 정보가 입수될 때까지
We have to go
into 24-hour
24시간 내내 보호해야겠어요
protective detail
until further notice.
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
What exactly does that mean?
우린 헤어질 수 없고
같이 살아야 한다는거에요
It means we can't break up,
and we have to move in together.
엘리가 보고 있으니까
믿게 해주는게 좋겠죠
Well, Ellie's watching.
We better sell it.
정말 확신해요?
Are you sure
about this?
정말 강한 사람이니까
아무 말 안 할수도 있잖아요
I mean, he's a really tough guy.
Maybe he won't talk.
척, 다들 결국엔 말해요
Chuck, everyone talks.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)